# Gwenaëlle DUMOULIN

FRONT-END DEVELOPER - 5 years of experience

(HTML / CSS / JS / JQuery)

- Daily use of Git

#### **EXPERIENCE**

03/2021 - 07/2023

**Frontend Developer Team Leader** 

**AB Tasty** 













03/2018 - 07/2020

Web Developer

Team Leader

Maxiweb



- Managing and leading the development team

- Development of complex client campaigns

- Conducting technical feasibility studies

- React / TypeScript / Jest development

- Management and supervision of the international

- Identifying potential training areas and implementing a

- Drafting job descriptions and conducting recruitment

development team (Communication via Slack) - Weekly presentations of new features in English

- Defining team goals and evaluating progress

- Creating innovative tools

technical training plan

interviews

- Managing the production of various launched projects
- Integrating email templates and landing pages while ensuring compatibility across ISPs and browsers (HTML / CSS)
- Implementing and securing GDPR-compliant forms (JavaScript, JQuery, PHP, and MySQL)
- Connecting forms to clients' CRMs (via API)
- Handling technical requests from clients
- Resolving various technical issues
- Configuring the tracking interface
- Conducting technological watch

2011 - 2018

Chemical **Technician**  Various experiences in the field of chemistry (material analysis, etc.)

#### **EDUCATION**

2018

Bac+2 **IT Career Change**  **Junior Web Developer Certificate** 

OpenClassrooms

**Bachelor's Degree in Chemistry** 

Paris-Sud 11 University

Chemistry

Associate's Degree in Chemistry (DUT)

**IUT of Orsay** 



Bac +3



## PROFILE -

Front-end developer with solid experience in JavaScript and TypeScript, I've grown into a leadership role, combining technical skills with team management. Curious and self-driven, I thrive in complex projects where innovation and code quality are key. Continuous learning and knowledge sharing are central to my approach for achieving team success.

#### CONTACT -

in https://www.linkedin.com/in/gwenaelle-dumoulin/

+33 6 89 83 09 64

gwen.dumoulin@gmail.com

#### SKILLS

HTML/CSS

JavaScript

jQuery

PHP React

## **LANGUAGES**

French

English

Spanish

## **HOBBIES**

- Reading
- Writing
- Piano
- **Fitness**